Register of the Karl August Wittfogel papers, 1728-1992
Hoover Institution Archives
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1907-1988.
  - Ladejinsky, Wolf I., 1954 (Folder 11)
  - Lambert, Sam, 1966-1967 (Folder 12)
  - Lancaster Press, 1949 (Folder 13)
  - Landshut, S., 1959 (Folder 14)
  - Lang, Olga
    - Undated (Folder 15)
    - 1929 (Folder 16)
    - 1933 (Folder 17)
    - 1934 (Folder 18)
    - 1935-1937 (Folder 19)
    - 1939-1961 (Folder 20)
    - 1968-1975 (Folder 21)
  - Lang, Margery, 1968 (Folder 22)
  - Larco Hoyle, Constante, 1955 (Folder 23)
  - Lasker, Bruno, 1936-1948 (Folder 24)
  - Lasker, Gabriel W., 1947 (Folder 25)
  - Lasky, Melvin J., 1951-1952 (Folder 26)
  - Lasswell, Harold D., 1946-1958 (Folder 27)
  - Latourette, Kenneth Scott, 1940-1950 (Folder 28)
  - Lattimore, Owen and Eleanor
    - 1935-1939 (Box 29., Folder 1)
    - 1940-1950 (Folder 2)
  - Lavender, William, 1966-1968 (Folder 3)
  - Lazarsfeld, Paul, 1968 (Folder 4)
  - Leach, Edward R., 1960-1961 (Folder 5)
  - Leap, William L., 1964-1974 (Folder 6)
  - LeCompte, Gare, 1960-1969 (Folder 7)
  - Lee, Dong Yoon, 1963 (Folder 8)
  - Lee, Orlan, 1964-1983 (Folder 9)
  - Lee, Shu-ching, 1946 (Folder 10)
  - Leers, Clara Olga Gesine and Fr. von, 1948-1974 (Folder 11)
  - Leers, Gesine von, 1974-1976 (Folder 12)
  - Lees, Susan H., 1977 (Folder 13)
  - Legters, Lyman H., 1973-1974 (Folder 14)
  - Lehning, Arthur, 1970-1971 (Folder 15)
  - Lennhoff, Herbert and Susan, 1959-1960 (Folder 16)
  - Lensen, George A., 1961 (Folder 17)
  - Leonard, Don and Carmen Cook de, 1954-1961 (Folder 18)
  - Leopold, Werner F., 1944-1947 (Folder 19)
  - Lerner, Max, 1955-1957 (Folder 20)
  - Lessing, Ferdinand D., 1940-1951 (Folder 21)
  - Levitas, Michael, n.d. (Folder 22)
  - Levy, Marion J., Jr., 1946-1958 (Folder 23)
  - Lewis, Winston G., 1966-1967 (Folder 24)
  - Lexington Books, 1974-1975 (Folder 25)
  - Li, An-che, 1947 (Box 30., Folder 1)
  - Li, Fang-kuei, 1951 (Folder 2)
  - Libertarian Book Club, 1972 (Folder 3)
  - Library of Congress, 1943-1961 (Folder 4)
  - Lichtenstein, David S., 1967 (Folder 5)
  - Liebman, Marvin, 1965-1969 (Folder 6)
  - Lien, Shih-sheng, 1938-1959 (Folder 7)
  - Lilly Endowment (John S. Lynn, Kenneth S. Templeton), 1962-1969 (Folder 8)
  - Lin, Tung-chi, 1946-1947 (Folder 9)
  - Lin, Yueh-hwa, 1944 (Folder 10)
  - Lindbeck, John, 1967 (Folder 11)
  - Lindsay of Birker, Lord Michael, 1959-1961 (Folder 12)
  - Lindt, Peter M., 1957 (Folder 13)
  - Linse, Ulrich, 1978 (Folder 14)
  - Linton, Ralph, 1943-1949 (Folder 15)
  - Lippe, Aschwin, 1951-1965 (Folder 16)
  - Lipset, Seymour M., 1959 (Folder 17)
  - Liu, James T., 1954-1962 (Folder 18)
  - Liu, Yu-wang, 1944 (Folder 19)
  - Lo, Jung-pang, 1959-1961. See also Wilhelm, Hellmut (Folder 20)
  - Lo, Karl, n.d. (Folder 21)
  - Lockwood, William W., 1948 (Folder 22)
  - Lodemann, Ernst and Inge, 1956-1959. Includes circular letter to Ernst Lodemann, Philipp Schultz, Georg Mindermann, Albert Buschle (Folder 23)
  - Loeber, D. A., 1977 (Folder 24)
  - Loewenstein, Karl, 1958 (Folder 25)
  - Loewenthal, Rudolf, 1953 (Folder 26)
  - Loh, Gene I-cheng, 1972-1973 (Folder 27)
  - London, Ivan D. and Maria, 1972-1985 (Folder 28)
  - London, Kurt L., 1962 (Folder 29)
  - London Institute of World Affairs, 1959-1961 (Folder 30)
  - Lopez Valdes, Pablo, 1969 (Folder 31)
  - Lotz, John, 1960 (Folder 32)
  - Loventhal, Milton, 1950 (Folder 33)
  - Lowe, Adolph, 1948 (Folder 34)
  - Lowe, Robert H., 1946 (Folder 35)
  - Lowenthal, Leo, 1971 (Folder 36)
  - Lozinski, B. Philip, 1959 (Folder 37)
  - Lubbe, Peter, 1983 (Folder 38)
  - Luce, Henry R., 1955 (Folder 39)
  - Ludowyk-Gyomroi, Edith, 1944-1945 (Folder 40)
  - Ludz, Peter C. and Ursula, 1976-1986 (Folder 41)
  - Lutzkendorf, Felix, 1977 (Folder 42)
  - Lyons, Eugene, 1953-1967 (Folder 43)
  - Ma, Smarlo, 1958 (Folder 44)
  - Maas, Walter, 1952-1953 (Folder 45)
  - McAuley, James, 1957-1961 (Folder 46)
  - McAvoy, T. T., 1955 (Folder 47)
  - Macdonald, Dwight, 1950-1963 (Folder 48)
  - McDonald, Earl, n.d. (Folder 49)
  - McDowell, Arthur G. and Janet, 1953-1966 (Folder 50)
  - McGraw-Hill Book Company, 1959 (Folder 51)
  - MacIver, R. M., 1946 (Folder 52)
  - McKee, Nancy, 1967-1969 (Folder 53)
  - Macmillan Company, 1946-1960 (Folder 54)
  - MacNair, Harley F., 1943-1946 (Folder 55)
  - MacNeish, Richard S., 1968-1979 (Folder 56)
  - Magnusson, Skuli, 1961 (Box 31., Folder 1)
  - Mah, Feng-hwa, 1962 (Folder 2)
  - Mainz, Rolf, 1982 (Folder 3)
  - Manhattanville College of the Sacred Heart, 1961-1964 (Folder 4)
  - Mann, Erika, 1939 (Folder 5)
  - Mantzke, Martin, 1967-1979 (Folder 6)
  - Marcuse, Herbert, 1935-1941 (Folder 7)
  - Marietti Editori, 1974 (Folder 8)
  - Marion Saunders Literary Agency, 1956-1959 (Folder 9)
  - Marquette University, 1960 (Folder 10)
  - Marsh, Robert M., 1961 (Folder 11)
  - Martin, Ben L., 1968-1972 (Folder 12)
  - Martin, Charles E., 1956-1959 (Folder 13)
  - Mary Baldwin College, 1969 (Folder 14)
  - Maryville College of the Sacred Heart, 1961-1967 (Folder 15)
  - Masani, Minoo R., 1954-1963 (Folder 16)
  - Massing, Paul W. and Herta, 1929-1979 (Folder 17)
  - Matsumoto, Mikio, 1958 (Folder 18)
  - Matsuo, M., 1954 (Folder 19)
  - Max Weber Centennial Commission, 1962 (Folder 20)
  - Mayrhofer, Manfred, 1973 (Folder 21)
  - Mead, Margaret, 1945 (Folder 22)
  - Mehnert, Klaus, 1958 (Folder 23)
  - Mehra, P. L., 1962 (Folder 24)
  - Mehta, Ghanshyam Dass, 1967-1973 (Folder 25)
  - Mehta, Narendra, 1957 (Folder 26)
  - Mendelsohn, I., 1949 (Folder 27)
  - Menges, Constantine C. and Nancy
    - 1961-1975 (Folder 28)
    - 1977-1981 (Folder 29)
  - Menges, Karl H.
    - Undated (Folder 30)
    - 1936-1958 (Folder 31)
    - 1960-1986 (Folder 32)
  - Menken, Jules, 1950-1957 (Box 32., Folder 1)
  - Menzies, James M., 1940 (Folder 2)
  - Merkel, Konrad, 1967 (Folder 3)
  - Merton, Robert K., 1946-1973 (Folder 4)
  - Meskill, John, 1963-1964 (Folder 5)
  - Metzger, Fred, 1964-1967 (Folder 6)
  - Meyer, Agnes E., 1940 (Folder 7)
  - Meyer, Frank S. and Elsie, 1955-1971 (Folder 8)
  - Michael, Franz H.
    - 1945-1949 (Folder 9)
    - 1950-1967 (Folder 10)
  - Millar, J. P. M., 1957 (Folder 11)
  - Miller, Meyer, 1967 (Folder 12)
  - Mindermann, Georg, 1957-1960 (Folder 13)
  - Minorsky, V., 1944-1947 (Folder 14)
  - Miret, Victoria, 1981 (Folder 15)
  - Misawa, Takeo, 1958-1960 (Folder 16)
  - Modern Age (David S. Collier, Eugene Davidson), 1960-1979 (Folder 17)
  - Modley, Rudolf, 1957-1967 (Folder 18)
  - Mohr, Erich, 1959 (Folder 19)
  - Moley, Malcolm, 1975 (Folder 20)
  - Molnar, Carin, 1968 (Folder 21)
  - Molnar, Thomas, n.d. (Folder 22)
  - Monash University, 1962-1970 (Folder 23)
  - Monat, 1950-1954 (Folder 24)
  - Mondadori Publishing Company, 1965-1966 (Folder 25)
  - Moore, Raymond A., Jr., 1960 (Folder 26)
  - Morgan, Arthur E., 1972 (Folder 27)
  - Morgenthau, Irma T., 1959 (Folder 28)
  - Mori, Katsumi, 1958 (Folder 29)
  - Morris, Morris David, 1956-1958 (Folder 30)
  - Morris, Robert, 1952-1987 (Folder 31)
  - Mortished, Ronald J. P., 1948-1950 (Folder 32)
  - Morton, John S. and Mary Jane, 1948-1952 (Folder 33)
  - Mosbach, Peter A., 1966 (Folder 34)
  - Mosely, Philip E., 1953-1967 (Folder 35)
  - Mostaert, A., 1948-1949 (Folder 36)
  - Mote, Frederick W., 1959-1967 (Folder 37)
  - Mote, Max, 1961 (Folder 38)
  - Moule, A. C., 1946-1947 (Folder 39)
  - Mount, Frank, 1970 (Folder 40)
  - Mueller, Franz H., 1955-1981 (Box 33., Folder 1)
  - Muhlen, Norbert, 1966-1974 (Folder 2)
  - Muldner, J. Heinrich, 1951-1952 (Folder 3)
  - Muller, F., 1914 (Folder 4)
  - Muller, Gert, 1964-1971 (Folder 5)
  - Muller, H. J., 1954 (Folder 6)
  - Mumford, Lewis, 1956 (Folder 7)
  - Munier, Jean-Jacques, 1964-1966 (Folder 8)
  - Murdock, George Peter, 1943-1961 (Folder 9)
  - Murphey, Rhoads, 1958-1959 (Folder 10)
  - Murphy, Richard W., 1962-1963 (Folder 11)
  - Muthmann, Gunther, 1978-1984 (Folder 12)
  - Myers, James T., 1963-1970 (Folder 13)
  - Myers, Margaret T., 1964 (Folder 14)
  - Myers, Ramon H., 1968 (Folder 15)
  - Nagase, Mamoru, 1967 (Folder 16)
  - Nahas, Anthony, 1983 (Folder 17)
  - Nakamura, Kikuo, 1959-1961 (Folder 18)
  - Naoi, Takeo, 1958 (Folder 19)
  - Narain, D., 1968-1970 (Folder 20)
  - National Book Foundation, 1958-1961 (Folder 21)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1972-1977 (Folder 22)
  - National Museums of Korea, 1949 (Box 34., Folder 1)
  - National Review (Priscilla L. Buckley, William F. Buckley, Jr., James Burnham, William A. Rusher, William S. Schlamm), 1956-1975. Includes correspondence with Clare Boothe Luce (Folder 2)
  - National Science Foundation, 1964-1973 (Folder 3)
  - Needham, Joseph, 1945-1950 (Folder 4)
  - Nelken, Tony, 1974-1975 (Folder 5)
  - Nelz, Walter, 1959-1960 (Folder 6)
  - Nest-Verlag, 1952 (Folder 7)
  - Neue China, Das, 1981 (Folder 8)
  - Neumann, Irmgard, 1959 (Folder 9)
  - Neumann, Siggi, 1949 (Folder 10)
  - New Leader (Moshe Decter, Norman G. Jacobs, Sol M. Levitas, Anatole Shub), 1949-1962 (Folder 11)
  - New Republic, n.d. (Folder 12)
  - New York Academy of Medicine (Iago Galdston), 1958-1960 (Folder 13)
  - New York Herald Tribune, 1936-1957 (Folder 14)
  - New York Times, 1951-1959 (Folder 15)
  - New York University Political Forum, 1967 (Folder 16)
  - Newark Museum, 1951 (Folder 17)
  - Newsweek, 1962 (Folder 18)
  - Nezu, Masashi, 1937-1941 (Folder 19)
  - Nicolaevsky, Boris I., 1946-1958 (Folder 20)
  - Nicolas, N. V., 1950 (Folder 21)
  - Niebuhr, Reinhold, 1957 (Folder 22)
  - Niebyl, Karl H., 1946 (Folder 23)
  - Niemeyer, Elizabeth D., 1970-1974 (Folder 24)
  - Niemeyer, Gerhart
    - Undated (Folder 25)
    - 1955-1958 (Folder 26)
    - 1959-1960 (Folder 27)
    - 1961-1967 (Folder 28)
    - 1977 (Folder 29)
  - Niewenhuize, Dr. van (University of Guelph), 1971 (Folder 1)
  - Niida, Noboru, 1957 (Folder 2)
  - Nishimura, Akio, 1967-1968 (Folder 3)
  - Nishino, Terutaro (National Diet Library), 1950-1953 (Folder 4)
  - Nixon, Richard M., 1960 (Folder 5)
  - Norddeutscher Rundfunk, 1959 (Folder 6)
  - North, Robert C., 1950-1953. Includes correspondence with Harold H. Fisher, Ford Foundation, Dan Lerner, Bertram D. Wolfe (Folder 7)
  - Northwestern University, 1961-1962 (Folder 8)
  - Notgemeinschaft der durch die Nurnberger Gesetze Betroffenen, 1947 (Folder 9)
  - Nove, Alec, 1967 (Folder 10)
  - Novey, Janet, 1978-1979 (Folder 11)
  - Nuova Vallecchi Editore, 1966-1978 (Folder 12)
  - Nutter, G. Warren, 1966 (Folder 13)
  - Odegaard, Charles E., 1951-1963 (Folder 14)
  - Ogura, K., 1935 (Folder 15)
  - Ohio State University, 1959 (Folder 16)
  - Ohira, Zengo, 1956-1963 (Folder 17)
  - Ohkawa, Kazushi, 1958-1974 (Folder 18)
  - Oklahoma State University (Bernard W. Eissenstat), 1973-1975 (Folder 19)
  - Ollman, Bertell, 1972 (Folder 20)
  - Olswaag, Margaret, 1968 (Folder 21)
  - Oort, H. A. van, 1962-1974 (Folder 22)
  - Opitz, Edmund A., 1959-1960 (Folder 23)
  - Opitz, Peter J., 1970-1973 (Folder 24)
  - Opler, Morris Edward, 1948 (Folder 25)
  - Oppenheim, A. L., 1953 (Folder 26)
  - Orchard, John E., 1947 (Folder 27)
  - Oriental Club of the City of New York, 1960-1963 (Folder 28)
  - Oriental Economist, 1958-1959 (Folder 29)
  - Orlando Committee (Alan G. Grant, Gerhart Niemeyer), 1954-1959 (Folder 30)
  - Ortlieb, H.-D., 1957 (Folder 31)
  - Oschilewski, Walter G., 1969 (Folder 32)
  - Osgood, Cornelius, 1949-1950 (Folder 33)
  - Ost-Probleme, 1950-1967 (Folder 34)
  - Oster's Books, 1956 (Folder 35)
  - Otto Harrassowitz Verlag, 1978 (Folder 36)
  - Outwater, John O., 1961 (Folder 37)
  - Overseas Press Club of America, 1968 (Folder 38)
  - Oxford University Press, 1938-1966 (Folder 39)
  - Paashe, John H., 1947-1948 (Folder 40)
  - Paetel, Karl O., 1941-1970 (Folder 41)
  - Palerm, Angel R. and Carmen
    - Undated (Box 36., Folder 1)
    - 1954-1959 (Folder 2)
    - 1960-1974 (Folder 3)
  - Palerm Viqueira, Juan Vicente, 1970-1976 (Folder 4)
  - Pan, Wei-tiu, 1935-1936 (Folder 5)
  - Pan American Union (Theo R. Crevenna, Javier Malagon), 1954-1967. See also Palerm, Angel R. (Folder 6)
  - Parpard, Auguste and Heini, 1946-1957 (Folder 7)
  - Parry, Stanley, 1957-1961 (Folder 8)
  - Pascal, Roy, 1949-1967 (Folder 9)
  - Passin, Herbert, 1966 (Folder 10)
  - Pasternak, Burton, 1967 (Folder 11)
  - Paxton, Diane, 1961 (Folder 12)
  - Peake, Cyrus H., 1939-1962 (Folder 13)
  - Peet, Richard (Antipode), 1983-1985 (Folder 14)
  - Pellicani, Luciano, 1982-1983 (Folder 15)
  - Pelliot, Paul, 1945 (Folder 16)
  - Pelzer, Karl J., 1949 (Folder 17)
  - Penniman, Howard, 1954-1967 (Folder 18)
  - Pennsylvania State University Press, 1965 (Folder 19)
  - Perez L., Marisol, 1967-1968 (Folder 20)
  - Petersen, William, 1958-1969 (Folder 21)
  - Peuker, Wilhelm and Hedwig, 1947-1976 (Folder 22)
  - Pfaffenhauser, Franz, 1973 (Folder 23)
  - Pfeiffenberger, Otto, 1943-1949 (Folder 24)
  - Philipp, Werner, 1966-1967 (Folder 25)
  - Philosophical Library, 1967 (Folder 26)
  - Pike, David, 1980 (Folder 27)
  - Piket-Lodemann, Inge, 1957-1978 (Folder 28)
  - Pinthus, Kurt, 1944-1947 (Folder 29)
  - Pipes, Richard E., 1959-1974 (Folder 30)
  - Plumhoff, Frida, 1948 (Box 37., Folder 1)
  - Poeschmann, Olga
    - Undated (Folder 2)
    - 1946-1949 (Folder 3)
    - 1950-1959 (Folder 4)
    - 1960-1970 (Folder 5)
  - Poliak, A. N., 1958 (Folder 6)
  - Pollard, Vincent K., 1969 (Folder 7)
  - Pollock, Frederick, 1935-1957 (Folder 8)
  - Pool, Ithiel de Sola, 1953 (Folder 9)
  - Poppe, Nicholas N., 1960-1969 (Folder 10)
  - Porter, Lewis C., 1938 (Folder 11)
  - Porzgen, Marie Theresa and Hermann, 1962 (Folder 12)
  - Posh, Udo and Dorrie, 1957-1963 (Folder 13)
  - Possony, Stefan T., 1962 (Folder 14)
  - Postmaster General, 1959 (Folder 15)
  - Powell, David E., 1972 (Folder 16)
  - Prandstraller, Gian Paolo, 1983 (Folder 17)
  - Praxis, 1979 (Folder 18)
  - President's Water Resources Policy Commission, 1950 (Folder 19)
  - Preuves, 1954 (Folder 20)
  - Price, Barbara J., 1971-1987 (Folder 21)
  - Price, Harry B., 1940 (Folder 22)
  - Princeton University (Marius B. Jansen, Richard W. Wilson), 1957-1973 (Folder 23)
  - Princeton University Press (Herbert S. Bailey, Jr.), 1960-1981 (Folder 24)
  - Pringsheim, Klaus H., 1961-1963 (Folder 25)
  - Pritchard, Earl H., 1950-1963 (Folder 26)
  - Pro und Contra, 1952 (Folder 27)
  - Public Affairs Press, 1956 (Folder 28)
  - Purpura, Mrs. Albert S. See Ricard, Ruth S.
  - Quaderni di Storia, 1983 (Folder 29)
  - Quadrant, 1956 (Folder 30)
  - Quickstad, Brian N., 1961-1964 (Folder 31)
  - Raddatz, Fritz J., 1978-1979 (Folder 32)
  - Rader, Melvin, 1963-1965 (Folder 33)
  - Raditsa, Bogdan, 1962-1981 (Folder 34)
  - Radkau, Joachim, 1983 (Folder 35)
  - Radtke, Kurt Werner, 1978 (Folder 36)
  - Random House, 1977-1982 (Folder 37)
  - Rankin, Karl Lott, 1973 (Folder 38)
  - Ratliff, William E.
    - Undated (Box 38., Folder 1)
    - 1965-1969 (Folder 2)
    - 1970-1986 (Folder 3)
  - Rea, Julio and Nona, 1955 (Folder 4)
  - Reclam, 1988 (Folder 5)
  - Redfield, Robert, 1947-1952 (Folder 6)
  - Regler, Gustav, 1940-1957 (Folder 7)
  - Reichel, Karl Ferdinand, 1947 (Folder 8)
  - Reichauer, Edmund, 1939-1946 (Folder 9)
  - Reid, Natasha, 1956-1967 (Folder 10)
  - Reif, Adelbert, 1982 (Folder 11)
  - Reifler, Erwin, 1948-1963 (Folder 12)
  - Reimer, Steven C., 1980-1982 (Folder 13)
  - Reinhardt, Ilse, 1947 (Folder 14)
  - Reischauer, Edwin O., 1940-1969 (Folder 15)
  - Reiss, Erich and Lotte Jacobi, 1948-1950. Includes correspondence with Richard Mather Bacon (Folder 16)
  - Relm Foundation
    - 1958-1959 (Box 39., Folder 1)
    - 1960-1961 (Folder 2)
    - 1962-1964 (Folder 3)
    - 1965-1967 (Folder 4)
    - 1968-1977 (Folder 5)
  - Remer, C. F., 1929-1934 (Folder 6)
  - Renn, Ludwig, 1938-1939 (Folder 7)
  - Reprint Publishers, 1971-1975 (Folder 8)
  - Reshetar, John S., Jr., 1964 (Folder 9)
  - Review of Politics (Waldemar Gurian), 1950-1961 (Folder 10)
  - Revista de Occidente, 1963-1964 (Folder 11)
  - Rhoads, Grace, 1938-1953 (Folder 12)
  - Ricard, Ruth S.
    - Undated (Box 40., Folder 1)
    - 1947 (Folder 2)
    - 1950 (Folder 3)
    - 1964-1975 (Folder 4)
  - Richardson, Hugh, 1966 (Folder 5)
  - Richardson Foundation, 1955-1960 (Folder 6)
  - Richter, Elihu. See Woloch, Isser
  - Richter, Luba O., 1962 (Folder 7)
  - Rieger, Charles, 1971 (Folder 8)
  - Riesman, David, 1947-1958 (Folder 9)
  - Rindle, Robert, 1949 (Folder 10)
  - Rizzoli Editore Corporation, 1965 (Folder 11)
  - Rizzotti, Martino, 1982 (Folder 12)
  - Roberts, Henry L., 1956-1961 (Folder 13)
  - Roberts, William M., Jr., 1963 (Folder 14)
  - Robertson, Walter S., 1957-1967 (Folder 15)
  - Robinson, Dwight E., 1963-1967 (Folder 16)
  - Robinson, Geroid T., 1950 (Folder 17)
  - Rochlin, R. P., 1967-1969 (Folder 18)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1951-1959 (Folder 19)
  - Ronald Press Company, 1945 (Folder 20)
  - Ronso-sha Company, 1961-1964 (Folder 21)
  - Roosevelt, Edith Kermit, 1959-1961 (Folder 22)
  - Rosendahl, Ernest and Erika, 1952-1986 (Folder 23)
  - Rosenfeld, Kurt, 1937-1939 (Folder 24)
  - Rosenthal, Harry Kenneth, 1973 (Folder 25)
  - Rostow, Eugene, 1963-1967 (Folder 26)
  - Rouchek, Joseph S., 1957-1960 (Folder 27)
  - Rousset, David, 1961 (Folder 28)
  - Rowe, David N., 1946-1972 (Folder 29)
  - Rowohlt Taschenbuch Verlag, 1972 (Folder 30)
  - Roys, Ralph L., 1962 (Folder 31)
  - Rubel, Maximilien, 1951-1960 (Folder 32)
  - Rue, John E., 1963 (Folder 33)
  - Ruhr-Universitat Bochum, 1979 (Folder 34)
  - Rumney, David, 1983-1984 (Folder 35)
  - Russian Institute, 1948-1968 (Folder 36)
  - Russian Review (Dimitri von Mohrenschildt), 1962 (Folder 37)
  - Ruter, A. J. C., 1959-1965 (Folder 38)
  - Rutgers, Sebald and Bartha, 1938-1946 (Folder 39)
  - Rutgers University Library, 1965 (Folder 40)
  - S. Fischer Verlag, 1983 (Box 41., Folder 1)
  - SOAK-Verlag (Karl Nolle), 1976-1985. Includes correspondence with Michael Buckmiller (Folder 2)
  - Saggiatore, 1972 (Folder 3)
  - Sahl, Hans, 1952 (Folder 4)
  - Salinger, Gerhard, 1949-1967 (Folder 5)
  - Salmony, Alfred, 1950 (Folder 6)
  - Salter, Katharine Hayden, 1939 (Folder 7)
  - Samolin, William, 1958 (Folder 8)
  - Samuels, Marwyn S., 1967-1982 (Folder 9)
  - Sanchez, Luis-Alberto, 1959-1961 (Folder 10)
  - Sander, Hans-Dietrich, 1962-1971 (Folder 11)
  - Sanders, Sol W., 1968 (Folder 12)
  - Sanders, William T., 1971-1980 (Folder 13)
  - Santamaria, Robert A., 1970-1975 (Folder 14)
  - Saran, Mary M., 1957-1971 (Folder 15)
  - Sarkisyanz, E., n.d. (Folder 16)
  - Saturday Review, 1954-1957 (Folder 17)
  - Sauer, Carl O., 1954 (Folder 18)
  - Savage, Gladys, 1951 (Folder 19)
  - Sawer, Marian, 1975 (Folder 20)
  - Scalapino, Robert A., 1968 (Folder 21)
  - Schafer, Edward H., 1958 (Folder 22)
  - Schantz, Roy N., 1958-1962 (Folder 23)
  - Schapiro, Leonard B., 1958-1979 (Folder 24)
  - Schefold, Bertram, 1982-1985 (Folder 25)
  - Schelhase, Marieshen and Ferdinand, 1947-1949 (Folder 26)
  - Schickele, Rainer, 1967 (Folder 27)
  - Schiebel, Joseph and Pat
    - Undated (Folder 28)
    - 1962-1976 (Folder 29)
  - Schiller, Otto, 1967 (Box 42., Folder 1)
  - Schlesinger, Arthur, Jr., 1951-1952 (Folder 2)
  - Schlesinger, Rose, 1929 (Folder 3)
  - Schlesinger, Rudolf and Mila, 1914-1939 (Folder 4)
  - Schmidt, Johann and Anna, 1934-1940 (Folder 5)
  - Schmidt, Mieze, 1950 (Folder 6)
  - Schmutz, Georges-Marie, 1985 (Folder 7)
  - Schocken Books, 1964 (Folder 8)
  - Schram, Stuart R., 1959-1964 (Folder 9)
  - Schroder, Elly, 1947-1951 (Folder 10)
  - Schroeder, Albert H., 1959 (Folder 11)
  - Schubert, Edmund and Marianne, 1956-1986 (Folder 12)
  - Schubert, Gerda, 1974-1975 (Folder 13)
  - Schubring, W., 1950 (Folder 14)
  - Schulenberg, Wolfgang, 1973-1975 (Folder 15)
  - Schultheis, Frederick D., 1958 (Folder 16)
  - Schultz, Philipp and Ina, 1957-1960 (Folder 17)
  - Schultz, William R., 1950 (Folder 18)
  - Schulze, Theo, 1947-1948 (Folder 19)
  - Schunemann, Minna, 1947 (Folder 20)
  - Schurmann, H. F., 1952 (Folder 21)
  - Schutzverband deutscher Schriftsteller, 1933 (Folder 22)
  - Schuyler, Steven, 1979 (Folder 23)
  - Schwab, Federico, 1955 (Folder 24)
  - Schwartz, Benjamin I., 1940-1950 (Folder 25)
  - Schwarz, Henry G., 1967 (Folder 26)
  - Schwarzschild, Henry, 1958-1963 (Folder 27)
  - Schweinfurth, Meide? 1967-1979 (Folder 28)
  - Schweitzer, Dr., 1959 (Folder 29)
  - Schwiebert, Erich, 1948 (Folder 30)
  - Schwiedrzik, Wolfgang M., 1982-1983 (Folder 31)
  - Science, 1959 (Folder 32)
  - Scott, John, 1962-1967 (Folder 33)
  - Seidel, Anna, 1966 (Folder 34)
  - Seiden, Jacob, 1966-1973 (Folder 35)
  - Seki, Yoshihiko, 1958-1965 (Folder 36)
  - Seligman, C., 1938 (Folder 37)
  - Senne, Wolfgang, 1979-1980 (Folder 38)
  - Seton-Watson, Hugh, 1960-1963 (Folder 39)
  - Shabad, Theodore, 1960 (Folder 40)
  - Shachtman, Max, 1971 (Folder 41)
  - Shapiro, Harry, 1969 (Folder 42)
  - Shaygan-nik, Hassan, 1978 (Folder 43)
  - Shinkawa, D., 1933 (Folder 44)
  - Shryock, John, 1940 (Folder 45)
  - Siefer, Elisabeth, 1974-1987 (Folder 46)
  - Sieler, Willy, 1938 (Folder 47)
  - Silone, Darina, 1953-1964 (Folder 48)
  - Simmons, Ernest J., 1950 (Folder 49)
  - Simmons, Harry, 1970 (Folder 50)
  - Simon, Walter B., 1971 (Folder 51)
  - Simon and Schuster, 1969 (Folder 52)
  - Sims, Helo, 1955-1978 (Folder 53)
  - Sinclair, Upton, 1925-1926 (Folder 54)
  - Sjaardema, Henryk, 1961 (Box 43., Folder 1)
  - Skalnik, Peter, 1980 (Folder 2)
  - Slavic Review, 1965-1970 (Folder 3)
  - Smith, M. Estillie, 1975. Includes letter from Frances White (Folder 4)
  - Smith, Mary M., 1966-1973 (Folder 5)
  - Smith, Michael G., 1960-1961 (Folder 6)
  - Social Democrats, USA, 1975 (Folder 7)
  - Social Science Research Council, 1963-1968 (Folder 8)
  - Socialisme en Democratie, 1962 (Folder 9)
  - Socialist Commentary, 1953 (Folder 10)
  - Sociedad Asiatica, 1953-1955 (Folder 11)
  - Societa Editrice Il Mulino, 1957-1973 (Folder 12)
  - Societas Uralo-Altaica, 1959-1985 (Folder 13)
  - Society for French-American Affairs, 1967 (Folder 14)
  - Sociological Inquiry, 1969 (Folder 15)
  - Sociologus, 1955 (Folder 16)
  - Sofue, Takao, 1958 (Folder 17)
  - Somura, Yasunobu, 1957 (Folder 18)
  - Souvarine, Boris, 1953-1968 (Folder 19)
  - Soviet Survey (Walter Z. Laqueur), 1958-1960 (Folder 20)
  - Spalek, John M., 1977-1978 (Folder 21)
  - Spate, O. H. K., 1959 (Folder 22)
  - Special Operations Research Office, 1957-1958 (Folder 23)
  - Spector, Ivar, 1949 (Folder 24)
  - Spector, Stanley, 1948-1965 (Folder 25)
  - Speier, Hans, 1949 (Folder 26)
  - Speiser, E. A., 1946 (Folder 27)
  - Spengler, Tilman, 1977-1978 (Folder 28)
  - Sperber, Manes, 1955-1959 (Folder 29)
  - Spicer, Edward H., 1962 (Folder 30)
  - Spigelberg, Franklin, 1948 (Folder 31)
  - Spinden, Herbert J., 1946 (Folder 32)
  - Spiro, Melford E., 1959 (Folder 33)
  - Spuler, Bertold, 1949-1976 (Folder 34)
  - Staats-Herold Corporation, 1956-1957 (Folder 35)
  - Stadtarchiv Luneburg, 1966-1967 (Folder 36)
  - Stanford University Press, 1969 (Folder 37)
  - Starr, Mark, 1957-1959 (Folder 38)
  - Stein, E., 1950-1951 (Folder 39)
  - Stein, Roger B., 1963 (Folder 40)
  - Stein, Rolf, 1949 (Folder 41)
  - Stein, Sol, 1957-1958 (Folder 42)
  - Steiner, H. Arthur, 1951-1959 (Folder 43)
  - Steiner, Ilse and Karl, 1939-1948 (Folder 44)
  - Stern, 1981 (Folder 45)
  - Stevens, David H., 1949-1950 (Folder 46)
  - Steward, Julian H. and Jane, 1954-1977 (Folder 47)
  - Storry, Richard (Oxford University), 1970-1971 (Box 44., Folder 1)
  - Stover, Leon E., 1960 (Folder 2)
  - Strasser, Edna G., 1972-1975 (Folder 3)
  - Strasser, Rudolf G., 1958-1961 (Folder 4)
  - Strauss, Lewis L., 1963-1972 (Folder 5)
  - Strauzs-Hupe, Robert, 1959 (Folder 6)
  - Strayer, Joseph R., 1960 (Folder 7)
  - Strong, William Duncan, 1941-1946 (Folder 8)
  - Stubel, H., 1953-1954 (Folder 9)
  - Studies on Asia, 1962 (Folder 10)
  - Stumer, Louis M., 1955-1957 (Folder 11)